Guide to the Arabic Film Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Posters, 1935-2005; Series I
  - Syria
    - Mughamarat ghawwar fi istanbul, undated (Box 81)
    - Wada'an lilams, undated (Box 81)
    - Wajih akhar lilhub [two posters], 1973 (Box 81)
    - Hawi mashakil, 1974 (Box 81)
    - Nasim al-ruh, 1998 (Box 81)
    - Maqlab mina al-maksik [two posters], 1972 (Box 81)
    - Sayd al-rijal [two posters], undated (Box 81)
  - English Language Posters
    - Les miserables [Egypt], 1978 (Box 81)
    - Omar mukhtar [Egypt], 1981 (Box 81)
    - The walls [Iraq], undated (Box 81)
    - West bayrouth [Lebanon], undated (Box 81)
    - Devil of island [Syria], 1978 (Box 81)
- Lobby Cards, 1948-1993; Series II
  The series is arranged aphabetically by country.
  - Egypt
    - Bawabit iblis [two cards], 1993 (Box 82)
    - Ibn min fi al-mujtama', 1979 (Box 82)
    - Al-'adhab imra'ah, 1977 (Box 82)
    - Al-batiniyah, 1980 (Box 82)
    - Sibyan wa banat [two cards], 1965 (Box 82)
    - Ghayat al-shayatin [two cards], undated (Box 82)
    - Bulbul afandi [three cards], 1948 (Box 82)
    - Jawz mirati [five cards], 1961 (Box 82)
    - Abi fawqa al-shajarah [two cards], 1969 (Box 82)
    - 'Antar ibn shaddad [three cards], 1960 (Box 83)
    - Al-dahaya [four cards], 1975 (Box 83)
    - Al-mustahil [three cards], 1965 (Box 83)
    - Min ajil hanafi [three cards], 1964 (Box 83)
    - Afwah wa aranib [three cards], 1977 (Box 83)
    - Ibnati al-'azizah, undated (Box 83)
    - Lu'bit al-hub wa al-jawaz [two cards], 1964 (Box 83)
    - Anisat wa sayyidat, 1974 (Box 83)
    - Sa'a'ud bila dumu', 1979 (Box 83)
    - Wadi al-dhikrayat, undated (Box 83)
    - Shillayt al-muhtalin, undated (Box 83)
    - Al-'ashiqah [two cards], undated (Box 83)
    - La tabki.. ya habib al-'umir, 1979 (Box 83)
    - Al-mudhnibun [two cards], 1976 (Box 84)
    - Shabab yarqus fawq al-nar [two cards], 1978 (Box 84)
    - Al-saqamat, undated (Box 84)
    - Hadha huwa al-hub [three cards], undated (Box 84)
    - Gharamiyat majnun [two cards], 1967 (Box 84)
    - Al-mamalik [two cards], undated (Box 84)
    - Al-ikhtiyar [three cards], undated (Box 84)
    - Amirit al-'arab [five cards], 1963 (Box 84)
    - Amirit...hubi ana [two cards], 1974 (Box 84)
    - Mabka al-'ushshaq, 1966 (Box 84)
    - Al-'a'ilah al-karimah, 1964 (Box 84)
    - Al-shayatin fi ijazah [two cards], 1972 (Box 84)
    - Al-ribat al-muqaddas [six cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Al-shaqiqan [two cards], 1965 (Box 85)
    - Ijazit sayif [two cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Al'aydi al-na'imah [three cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Ashraf khati'ah [three cards], 1973 (Box 85)
    - Al-daya' [six cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Fi tariqi rajul [three cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Dhikra laylit hub [two cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Bayya' al-khawatim [four cards], undated (Box 85)
    - Binit 'antar, undated (Box 85)
    - Jannah wa nar, undated (Box 86)
    - Abu ahmad, 1960 (Box 86)
    - Almumya', undated (Box 86)
    - Ughniyah 'ala al-mamar, 1972 (Box 86)
    - Ijazit sayf, undated (Box 86)
    - Bambah kashshar, 1974 (Box 86)
    - Rabi'ah al-'adawiyah, 1963 (Box 86)
    - Al-harami, undated (Box 86)
    - Risalah min imra'ah majhulah, 1962 (Box 86)
    - Shati' al-masatil, 1983 (Box 86)
    - Qasir al-shuq, undated (Box 86)
    - Rajul fi sijin al-nisa', 1982 (Box 86)
    - Nadyah, undated (Box 86)
    - Sayyid darwish, undated (Box 86)
    - Alif laylah wa laylah, 1964 (Box 86)
    - Shaqawit rijalah, undated (Box 86)
    - Al-zawaj al-sa'id, undated (Box 86)
    - Al-rijal la yatazawajun al-jamilat, undated (Box 86)
    - Mudhakarat al-anisah manal [four cards], undated (Box 86)
    - Mulid ya dunia [three cards], 1975 (Box 86)
    - Miramar, 1969 (Box 87)
    - 'Itab [two cards], undated (Box 87)
    - Shilni wa ashilak [two cards], 1977 (Box 87)
    - La tatrukni wahdi [two cards], 1973 (Box 87)
    - Al-kharsa' [two cards], 1961 (Box 87)
    - Haribat min al-hub [two cards], undated (Box 87)
    - Aghla min hayati [two cards], undated (Box 87)
    - Shay' fi hayati, undated (Box 87)
    - Yawm al-ahad al-dami, 1975 (Box 87)
    - Shanabu fi al-misyadah, undated (Box 87)
  - Lebanon
    - Hamsit al-shaytan, 1969 (Box 87)
    - Al-ghajariah al-'ashiqah, 1972 (Box 87)
    - Lu'bit al-haz [two cards], 1968 (Box 87)
    - Al-bank [two cards], 1965 (Box 87)
    - Ahlan bi al-hub, 1968 (Box 87)
    - La'ib al-kurah, undated (Box 87)
  - Syria
    - Al-ra'yah al-hasna' [three cards], undated (Box 88)
    - 'Arus min dimashq [two cards], 1975 (Box 88)
    - Habibi majnun jidan, undated (Box 88)
    - Al-sa'alik [two cards], undated (Box 88)
    - Al-tha'lab [three cards], 1971 (Box 88)
    - Samak bala hasak [two cards], 1977 (Box 88)
    - Hawi mashakil [two cards], 1974 (Box 88)
    - Ana 'antar [two cards], undated (Box 88)
    - Banat lilhub [two cards], undated (Box 88)
    - Lu'bit al-shaytan [two cards], undated (Box 88)
    - Ghawar jayms bond [three cards], 1974 (Box 88)
- Press Books, 1954-1989; Series III
  The series is arranged alphabetically by country.
  - Egypt
    - Junun al-hub, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Ibnati al-'azizah, undated (Box 89)
  - Badi'ah masabni, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-'adhab fawq shifah tartajef, 1974 (Box 89)
  - Ward wa shawk, 1970 (Box 89)
  - Mughamarat fi Istanbul, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Sunya wa al-majnun, 1976 (Box 89)
  - Hasan wa marika, undated (Box 89)
  - Rihlit al-nisyan, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Liman tashruq al-shams, 1977 (Box 89)
  - 7 ayam fi al-janah, undated (Box 89)
  - Sa'ah.. jawaz, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-mala'in, 1979 (Box 89)
  - 'Usfur al-sharq, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-bahith 'an fadihah, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-ashrar, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Al-shayatin wa al-kurah, undated (Box 89)
  - Arjuk.. i'tini hadha al-dawa', undated (Box 89)
  - Hub la ansah, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-mudir al-fani, 1965 (Box 89)
  - Sikritayr mama, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-ghifran, undated (Box 89)
  - Shay' fi sadri, undated (Box 89)
  - Qalb al-layl, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Shayatin ila al-abad, 1974 (Box 89)
  - Qublah fi libnan, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-harib, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Shillayt al-murahiqin, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Hub ahla min al-hub, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Bayt bila hanan, undated (Box 89)
  - Ya rab tubah, 1957 (Box 89)
  - 'Ish al-gharam, undated (Box 89)
  - Wa islamah, undated (Box 89)
  - Hayat khatirah, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-mushaghib, 1965 (Box 89)
  - Bayna al-ssama' wa al-ard, undated (Box 89)
  - Bayt min rimal, undated (Box 89)
  - Zuhur bariyyah, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Ashraf khati'ah, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Al-ikhtiyar, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-jarimah wa al-'iqab, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-khatafin, 1972 (Box 89)
  - Bambah kashshar, 1974 (Box 89)
  - Bint 'antar, undated (Box 89)
  - Wa thalithuhum al-shaytan, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Ibnati wa al-dhi'b, 1977 (Box 89)
  - Fi tariqi rajul, undated (Box 89)
  - 'Ala waraq sulufan, undated (Box 89)
  - Anqidhu hadhihi al-'ailah, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Al-mazika fi khatar, undated (Box 89)
  - Bi'r al-hirman, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-faris al-aswad, 1954 (Box 89)
  - La'nit imra'ah, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Dhi'ab 'ala al-tariq, undated (Box 89)
  - Yadu Allah, undated (Box 89)
  - Malikat al-jamal, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-mazahir, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-tirjman, undated (Box 89)
  - Hub wa kibriya', 1972 (Box 89)
  - Bilal, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-abtal, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Al-mar'ah al-ukhra, undated (Box 89)
  - Ayam fi al-halal, undated (Box 89)
  - 'Aris li'ukhti, undated (Box 89)
  - Laylit hub akhirah, undated (Box 89)
  - Rajul fi sijin al-nisa', 1982 (Box 89)
  - Nadiah, undated (Box 89)
  - 'Asifah min al-dumu', 1979 (Box 89)
  - Bila rahmah, 1971 (Box 89)
  - Nassir 56, undated (Box 89)
  - Ah min hawa', undated (Box 89)
  - Adham al-sharqawi, undated (Box 89)
  - Fi al-ssayf lazim nihib, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-shayatin fi ijazah, 1972 (Box 89)
  - 5 shari' al-habayib, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Nur al-din wa al-baharah al-thalathah, undated (Box 89)
  - Shari' muhammad 'ali, undated (Box 89)
  - Ibn al-hadad, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-fannan al-'azim, undated (Box 89)
  - Ikspris al-hub, undated (Box 89)
  - Imbraturiaht mim, undated (Box 89)
  - Mursi fawq mursi taht, 1982 (Box 89)
  - Al-hayaht nagham, undated (Box 89)
  - Al-shaqah min haq al-zawjah, 1985 (Box 89)
  - Al-mujrim, 1954 (Box 89)
  - Lebanon (Box 89)
  - 'Aqid al-lu'lu', 1964 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Funduq al-ahlam, 1967 (Box 89)
  - Fidaki ya filastin, 1969 (Box 89)
  - Nisa' bila ghad, undated (Box 89)
  - Bint al-haris, undated (Box 89)
  - Mauwal, 1966 (Box 89)
    - 'Antar Fares al-sahra', undated (Box 89)
  - Syria (Box 89)
  - Maqlab min al-maksik, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Shanaw, undated (Box 89)
  - Wajeh akhar lilhub, 1973 (Box 89)
  - Maqlab hub, 1972 (Box 89)
  - Kifah hata al-tahrir, undated (Box 89)
- Half Sheets, 1949-1974; Series IV
  - Algeria
    - Al-afyun wa al-'asa, 1969 (Box 90)
  - Egypt
    - Qadi al-gharam, 1962 (Box 90)
    - La tatrukni wahdi, 1973 (Box 90)
    - Al-nassabin al-thalathah, 1968 (Box 90)
    - Al-lahab, 1964 (Box 90)
    - Min ghayr mi'ad, 1962 (Box 90)
    - Al-majanin al-thalathah, 1970 (Box 90)
    - Gharam fi al-tariq al-zira'i, 1971 (Box 90)
    - Ashraf khati'ah, 1972 (Box 90)
    - Rajul fi al-zalam, 1963 (Box 91)
    - Al-mukhadi'un, 1973 (Box 91)
    - Hawwa' wa al-qird, undated (Box 91)
    - 'Aylit zizi, 1963 (Box 91)
    - Nihayit al-shayatin, 1970 (Box 91)
    - 'Ish al-gharam, 1959 (Box 91)
    - 'Antar ibn shaddad, 1949 (Box 91)
    - 'Ala difaf al-nil, 1963 (Box 91)
    - 'A'ilat muhtaramah, 1969 (Box 91)
    - Du'a' al-karawan, 1959 (Box 92)
    - Al-sahirah al-saghirah, 1963 (Box 92)
    - Salasil min harir, 1962 (Box 92)
    - Shabab yahtariq, 1972 (Box 92)
    - Shayatin al-layl, 1966 (Box 92)
    - Al-shayatin al-thalathah, 1964 (Box 92)
    - Abi fawqa al-shajarah, 1969 (Box 92)
    - Ajmal ayyam hayati, 1974 (Box 92)
    - Ihna al-talamdhah, 1959 (Box 92)
    - Um al-'arusah, 1962 (Box 93)
    - Ah min hawwa', 1962 (Box 93)
    - Bambah kashshar, 1974 (Box 93)
    - Bint badi'ah, 1972 (Box 93)
    - Al-hub al-khalid, 1965 (Box 93)
    - Dunya al-banat, 1962 (Box 93)
    - Fayruz, undated (Box 94)
    - Mudhakkarat tilmidhah, 1962 (Box 94)
    - Ma'budit al-jamahir, undated (Box 94)
    - Al-ibn al-mafqud, 1964 (Box 94)
    - Ijazit sayf, 1967 (Box 94)
  - Lebanon (Box 94)
  - Al-qahirun, 1966 (Box 94)
  - Bint 'antar, 1964 (Box 94)
- Fragile Posters - Egypt, 1956-1961, undated; Series V
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in boxes 95-100 are closed due to their physical condition. Researchers must obtain permission in writing from the Near Eastern Collection Curator to obtain access.
  - Egypt
    - Inta habibi, undated (Box 95)
    - Ibn hamidu, undated (Box 95)
    - Hamidu, undated (Box 96)
    - Tariq al-dumu', 1961 (Box 96)
    - Shaytan al-sahra', undated (Box 97)
    - Al-ribat al-muqaddas, undated (Box 97)
    - Al-jarimah wa al-'iqab, undated (Box 97)
    - Shari' al-hub, undated (Box 98)
    - Imra'ah fi al-tariq, undated (Box 98)
    - Nafidhah 'ala al-jannah, undated (Box 98)
    - Ghaltit habibi, 1958 (Box 99)
    - Al-namrud, 1956 (Box 99)
    - Tariq al-amal, undated (Box 100)
    - Yahya al-fan, undated (Box 100)
    - Nihayit hub, 1957 (Box 100)
    - Malak wa shaytan, 1960 (Box 100)